Guide to the Trade catalogs collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- F
  - Fairbanks, Morse, and Company (Chicago, Ill., etc.), 1914–1941; Uai +F158; 4 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1099)
    Oil engines
  - Fairchild Brothers and Foster (New York, N.Y.), 1939; Uai F163; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1100)
  - Fairmount Aluminum Company (Fairmount, W. Va.), 1949; Uai F166; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1101)
    Aluminum rolling mill products
  - Fairway Laboratories, Inc. (St. Louis, Mo.), 1938; Uai +F17; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1102)
    Fairway salt tablets and dispensers
  - Fales and Jenks, 1922; Uai F18; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1103)
    Ring spinning frames
  - Falk and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1949; Uai +F187; 4 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1104)
    Oils and resins
  - Farnsworth Television and Radio Corporation (Fort Wayne, Ind.), 1941; Uai F237; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1105)
    Capehart radio phonograph
  - Farquhar, A.B., Company, Ltd. (York, Pa.), undated; Uai F239; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1106)
    Ajax portable engines
  - Farrel-Birmingham Company, Inc. (Ansonia, Conn.), 1942; Uai +F247; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1107)
    Stone crushers
  - Faure and Kessler (Clermont-Ferrand, France), 1874; Uai F274; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1108)
    Pan-apparatus for the concentration of sulphuric acid
  - Fawcett Ventilated Fireproof Building Company, Ltd. (Philadelphia, Pa.), undated; Uai F283; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1109)
    Fireproof building materials
  - Fay, J.A., and Egan Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), Uai F29
    Woodworking machinery
    - 1907–1913, 2 volumes (Box 107)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 108)
  - Fedders-Quigan Corporation (Buffalo, N.Y.), undated; Uai +F316; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1110)
    Radiators
  - Federal Products Corporation (Providence, R.I.), 1931–1934; Uai +F317; 5 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1111)
    Gauges, Measuring instruments, etc.
  - Federal Radio Corporation, 1928; Uai F318; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1112)
    "Ortho-sonic" federal radios
  - Fellowcrafters (Boston, Mass.), 1932; Uai +F334; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1113)
    Handicraft supplies
  - Fellows Company of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1911–1913; Uai F335; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1114)
    Diagnostic methods
  - Fenton Label Company, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1916–1923; Uai F367; 3 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1115)
    Gummed labels and advertising stickers
  - Ferranti, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1930; Uai F411; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1116)
    Amplifying equipment
  - Ferrario, Fratelli (Milan, Italy), 1885–1886; Uai +F412; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1117)
  - Ferro Machine and Foundry Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1907–1909; Uai +F417; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1118)
    Engines, etc.
  - Ferry, D.M., and Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1885–1886; Uai +F419; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1119)
  - Fiat Metal Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1929; Uai +F442; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1120)
    Fiat showers
  - Filer and Stowell Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1856–1905; Uai F474; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1121)
    Saw mill machinery
  - Filing Equipment Bureau, Inc. (Boston, Mass.), 1931; Uai F476; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1122)
    Flexi-flash signals
  - Finch and Apgar (Ithaca, N.Y.), 1884; Uai +F492; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1124)
    "Cleaves" drawing, writing, and study table
  - Finch, W.S. (Toronto, Canada), 1889; Uai F491; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1123)
    Wood preservative
  - Finchley Establishment (New York, N.Y., Chicago, Ill.), 1929; Uai F493; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1125)
    Men's clothing and haberdashery
  - Finley, Freeman J. (New York, N.Y.), 1900; Uai +F496; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1126)
    Initials, Monograms, Ebony goods, Badges
  - Fire Annihilator Company (London, England), 1851; Uai F512; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1127)
    Fire extinguisher
  - Fire-proof Building Company of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1874; Uai +F514; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1128)
    Fire-proof building materials
  - Fire-proof Door Company (New York, N.Y.), 1905; Uai F5143; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1129)
    Fire-proof doors, shutters, and metal covered interior finish
  - Fire-proof Furniture and Construction Company (Miamisburg, Ohio), 1915; Uai F5145; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1130)
    Security filing cases
  - Firestone Industrial Products (Akron, Ohio), 1944; Uai +F5159; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1131)
    Firestone "Velon" and "Foamex" products
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Company (Akron, Ohio), 1909–1937; Uai +F516; 5 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1132-1133)
    Auto supplies, etc.
  - Firex Company of America (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai F517; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1134)
  - Firth-Sterling Steel Company (McKeesport, Pa.), 1920; Uai F519; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1135)
    Tool and die steels
  - Fischer Motor Corporation (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +F524; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1138)
    Fischer motors
  - Fischer, Georg (Schaffhausen, Switzerland), 1878; Uai +F523; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1136)
    Gas, water, and vapor utensils
  - Fischer, William G., Range and Furnace Works (Cincinnati, Ohio), undated; Uai +F5235; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1137)
    Iron ranges and furnaces
  - Fisher Body Corporation (Detroit, Mich.), 1928; Uai +F5345; 1 volume (Box 109)
    Automobile bodies
  - Fisher Scientific Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1926–1952; Uai +F537; 3 volumes (Box 105, Folder 1238-1239)
    Laboratory apparatus and furniture, Scientific instruments, etc.
  - Fisher and Davis Manufacturing Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1909; Uai F534; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1140)
    General machinery
  - Fisher and Porter Company (Hatboro, Pa.), 1943–1946; Uai +F5343; 12 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1141-1143)
    Rotameters
  - Fisher, S. (London, England), undated; Uai F533; 3 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1139)
    Luggage
  - Fisher-Price Toys, Inc. (East Aurora, N.Y.), 1934; Uai F536; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1144)
  - Fiske and Coleman (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai +F548; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1145)
    Fire brick, Cements, etc.
  - Flagg, Stanley G., and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1871–1876; Uai +F597; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1146)
    Iron and steel castings, etc.
  - Flather and Company (Nashua, N.H.), undated; Uai F616; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1147)
    Machine tools, Lathes, etc.
  - Fleming, James (New York, N.Y.), 1872–1877; Uai +F629; 2 volumes (Box 91, Folder 1148)
    Seeds, Bulbs, etc.
  - Fletcher Manufacturing Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1914; Uai F636; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1149)
    Electrical construction supplies
  - Fletcher-Stanley Company (New York, N.Y.), 1909; Uai F637; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1150)
    Electrical supplies and specialties
  - Flexible Door and Shutter Company (Worcester, Mass.), 1899–1900; Uai +F639; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1151)
    "Flexifold" specialties
  - Flicoteaux, Borne, and Boutet (Paris, France), 1900; Uai F641; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1152)
    Hospital equipment
  - Flicoteaux, Boutet, and Fleurot (Paris, France), 1934; Uai +F6411; 1 volume (Box 91, Folder 1153)
    Laboratory equipment
  - Flory, S., Manufacturing Company (Bangor, Pa.), 1908; Uai +F665; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1173)
    Hoisting engines, etc.
  - Flush-Tank Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1892; Uai +F675; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1174)
    Intermittent flush tanks
  - Foamite Firefoam Company (New York, N.Y.), 1921; Uai +F68; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1175)
    Fire foam apparatus
  - Fokker Aircraft Corporation (Kansas City, Mo.), 1926–1928; Uai +F695; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1176)
    Commercial airplanes
  - Folbot Corporation (Long Island City, N.Y.), 1942–1949; Uai +F697; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1177)
    Boats
  - Follansbee Brothers Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919; Uai F72; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1178)
    Tin plates and sheet steel
  - Folmer Graflex Corporation (Rochester, N.Y.), 1946; Uai F7285; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1180)
    Graflex photorecord
  - Folmer and Schwing Manufacturing Company (Rochester, N.Y., etc.), 1898–1906; Uai F728; 6 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1179)
    Photographic apparatus, etc.
  - Fontaine, Georges (Paris, France), 1888; Uai +F734; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1181-1182)
    Chemistry instruments and glassware
  - Foos Gas Engine Company (Springfield, Ohio), 1912; Uai +F738; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1183)
  - Foot, Barker and Company (Cleveland, Ohio), undated; Uai F739; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1184)
    Tool grinder
  - Ford Motor Company (Dearborn, Mich.), 1920–1941; Uai +F756; 5 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1189)
    Automobile parts, etc.
  - Ford, Bacon and Davis (New York, N.Y.), 1944; Uai +F754; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1188)
    Modern industrial plants
  - Ford, J.B., Company (Wyandotte, Mich.), 1930–1939; Uai +F752; 6 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1185)
    "Wyandotte" cleaning powders
  - Ford, J.S., Johnson and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1901–1903; Uai +F753; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1186-1187)
    Go-carts and perambulators
  - Fore River Ship and Engine Company (Quincy, Mass.), 1902; Uai +F761; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1190)
    Ships, etc.
  - Forman Company (New York, N.Y.), 1933; Uai +F765; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1191)
    Bronze tablets and letters
  - Fort Wayne Engineering and Manufacturing Company (Fort Wayne, Ind.), 1923; Uai F7755; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1192)
    Pumps and water systems
  - Foster Hardware Company (Meriden, Conn.), undated; Uai +F816; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1194)
    Cabinet hardware, Art brass, Bronze goods
  - Foster, Theordore W., and Brother Company (Providence, R.I.), 1911; Uai +F815; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1193)
    Toilet ware and jewelry
  - Fostoria Incandescent Lamp Company (Fostoria, Ohio), 1899; Uai +F818; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1195)
    Photometer
  - Fougera, E., and Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1913; Uai F823; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1196)
    Pharmaceutical specialties
  - Fountaingrove Vineyard Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1894–1898; Uai +F825; 10 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1197)
    Wines and brandies
  - Four Wheel Drive Sales Company (Clintonville, Wis.), 1931; Uai +F826; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1198)
    Trucks
  - Fowler and Company (Guilford, Conn.), undated; Uai +F829; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1199)
    Iron feeder and water dish
  - Fox-Becker Granite Company (Middletown, Conn.), 1907; Uai F833; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1200)
    Monuments, Statuary
  - Francis and Company (London, England), 1876; Uai +F847; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1201)
    Cement
  - Francis, Smith and Hawkes (Birmingham, England), undated; Uai +F848; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1202)
    Portable cockles
  - Francke and Schindler (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1887; Uai +F849; 1 volume (Box 106, Folder 1240)
    Builders' hardware, supplies, and mechanics' tools
  - Frank Leslie's Lady's Journal (New York, N.Y.), 1876–1877; Uai +F8515; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1204)
    Paper dress patterns
  - Frank Machinery Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1941; Uai +F8516; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1205)
  - Frank, R.H. (Marion, Ind.), 1903; Uai +F851; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1203)
  - Franklin Automobile Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1919–1930; Uai +F853; 3 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1208)
    Automobiles, Air-cooled motors
  - Franklin Company (Canton, Ohio), 1932; Uai F854; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1209)
    Heating systems
  - Franklin Electric Manufacturing Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1907–1910; Uai +F855; 16 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1210-1211)
    Lamps
  - Franklin, H.H., Manufacturing Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1905–1923; Uai +F852; 3 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1206-1207)
    Automobiles, Die-cast parts
  - Frasse, Peter A., and Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1916; Uai F864; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1212)
    Steel
  - Frick Company (Waynesboro, Pa.), 1893–1938; Uai +F9113; 5 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1214)
    Portable engines, Ice-making equipment, Air-conditioning, etc.
  - Frick, John (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +F911; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1213)
    Class, club, and society pins, Nautical medals, badges, and prize jewelry
  - Fricke and Stiller (Berlin, Germany), undated; Uai +F9116; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1215)
  - Friction Pivot Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1923; Uai F912; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1216)
    C.D.T. fixtures and hardware specialties
  - Frigidaire Corporation (Dayton, Ohio), 1929–1930; Uai F915; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1217)
    Refrigerators
  - Frimley (Auckland, New Zealand), 1912; Uai F916; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1218)
    Canned goods
  - Frink, I.P. (New York, N.Y.), 1882; Uai +F917; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1219-1220)
    Reflectors
  - Fritz, Max (Goerlitz, Germany), 1879–1881; Uai F919; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1221-1222)
    Projectors, Slides
  - Frost Insecticide Company (Arlington, Mass.), 1925–1933; Uai +F929; 5 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1224)
    Power sprayers, Insecticides, etc.
  - Frœbel and Company (Zürich, Switzerland), 1886–1887; Uai F922; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1223)
    Plants, etc.
  - Fuller Brush Company (Harford, Conn.), 1921–1950; Uai +F955; 2 volumes (Box 110)
  - Fuller and Johnson (St. Louis, Mo.), 1917; Uai F954; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1225)
    Motor lawn mowers
  - Fuller-Warren Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1905; Uai F957; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1226)
    Boilers, Radiators
  - Fulton Iron Works (San Francisco, Calif.), undated; Uai +F958; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1227)
    Gold and silver milling machinery
  - Fulton Sylphon Company (Knoxville, Tenn.), 1942; Uai +F959; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1228)
    Temperature regulators
  - Funk and Wagnalls Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4307)
    Books, etc.
  - Futaba Photo Company (Kobe, Japan), 1940; Uai F986; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1229)
    Lantern slides, etc.
- G
  - G.M.T. Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai G528; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1322)
    Concrete, plaster, and mortar mixer
  - Gaertner, Wm., and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1900; Uai G119; 4 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1230)
    Astronomical, physical, and physiological apparatus
  - Gallet, Lefebvre and Cie (Paris, France), 1867; Uai G135; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1231)
    Phospho-guano, Fertilizers
  - Galvaniserings-Aktiebolaget I Carlskrona (Carlskrona, Sweden), undated; Uai G139; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1232)
    Galvanized Swedish iron sheets
  - Gamewell Company (Newtown Upper Falls, Mass.), 1926; Uai +G145; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1233)
    "Herculite" fire alarm boxes
  - Gamewell Fire Alarm Telegraph Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911; Uai +G1451; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1234)
    Fire departments for industrial plants
  - Gandolfi, L., and Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai G152; 2 volumes (Box 104, Folder 1235)
    "Vov" tonic
  - Garin and Cie (Paris, France), undated; Uai G183; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1236)
  - Garratt, W.T. (San Francisco, Calif.), undated; Uai +G192; 1 volume (Box 104, Folder 1237)
    Pumping and hydraulic machinery
  - Garrity and McKay (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1912; Uai G193; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1250)
    Ventilated hoods, Asbestos fire proof hoods
  - Gates Radio Company (Quincy, Ill.), 1953; Uai +G223; 2 volumes (Box 115, Folder 1407-1408)
    Broadcasting, recording and communications equipment
  - Gaylord Brothers, Inc. (Syracuse, N.Y., etc.), 1941; Uai +G256; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1251)
    Library furniture and supplies
  - Gebhardt, J.F., Manufacturing Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1905; Uai G264; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1252)
    Carved moldings and corner blocks, Spindles, etc.
  - Geissler, Dr. H., Nachf. Franz Müller, firm (Bonn, Germany), 1881; Uai G278; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1253)
  - Gem Manufacturing Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912; Uai G284; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1254)
    Steel and brass oilers, Flexible shaft tools and attachments, etc.
  - Gemsco (New York, N.Y.), 1937–1939; Uai +G2845; 4 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1255)
    Uniform equipment, Novelties, etc.
  - General Box Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai +G28513; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1256)
    Shipping containers
  - General Chemical Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai G2852; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1257)
    Reagents and chemicals
  - General Electric Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), Uai +G2857
    Electrical appliances
    - 1893–1920, 70 volumes (Box 116, Folder 1409-1415)
    - 1926–1944, 30 volumes (Box 117, Folder 1416-1419)
    - 1941–1950, 5 volumes (Box 118, Folder 1420-1423)
    - 1930, 1 volume (Box 119, Folder 1424)
    - 1936, 1 volume (Box 120, Folder 1425)
    - 1936, 1 volume (Box 121)
  - General Electric Improvement Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai G286; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1258)
    Electric machinery, etc.
  - General Electric Supply Corporation (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1938–1949; Uai G2864; 3 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1259)
    Power and power line equipment, Heating devices, Motors, etc.
  - General Electric X-Ray Corporation (Chicago, Ill.), 1938; Uai +G2865; 26 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1260-1262)
    Temperature controls, VCT units, Films, Chemicals, etc.
  - General Fire Extinguisher Company (Providence, R.I.), 1902–1919; Uai +G287; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1263)
  - General Fireproofing Company (Youngstown, Ohio, etc.), 1910–1941; Uai +G2873; 17 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1264-1268)
    Metal lath, bar, mesh, and fabric reinforcement, "Allsteel" office equipment, etc.
  - General Foods Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1937; Uai +G2877; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1269)
    Food, Groceries, etc.
  - General Incandescent Arc Light Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +G288; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1270)
    Incandescent arc lamps
  - General Iron Works Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1929–1930; Uai +G2885; 3 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1271)
    "Hot-kold" heating systems, etc.
  - General Lead Batteries Company (Newark, N.J.), 1926; Uai G289; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1272)
    Radio batteries
  - General Liquid Air and Refrigerating Company (New York, N.Y.), 1898; Uai G2895; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1273-1274)
    Liquid air, etc.
  - General Motors Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1936–1943; Uai +G2898; 3 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1275)
  - General Motors Truck Company (Pontiac, Mich.), 1926–1935; Uai +G29; 2 volumes (Box 125)
    "Big Brute" trucks, "GMC-Wayne" school bus, etc.
  - General Office Equipment Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1930; Uai +G2915; 2 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1276)
    "Sunstrand" adding-figuring machines
  - General Radio Company (Cambridge, Mass.), 1916–1951; Uai G292; 4 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1277-1279)
    Radio laboratory apparatus
  - General Roofing Manufacturing Company (York, Pa., etc.), 1912; Uai G2923; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1280)
    Field tactics of salesmen
  - General Tire and Rubber Company, 1943; Uai G2925; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1281)
    Synthetic rubber
  - Geography Supply Bureau (Ithaca, N.Y.), undated; Uai G2946; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1282)
    Physical geography lantern slides
  - Geometric Tool Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1915–1924; Uai G295; 4 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1283-1284)
    Screw-cutting die heads, Threading machines, etc.
  - Gerdes, Theo. R. N. (New York, N.Y.), 1917; Uai G314; 1 volume (Box 112, Folder 1286)
    Gerdes electric window ventilation
  - Gerhardt, C. (Bonn am Rhein, Germany), 1877–1905; Uai +G315; 12 volumes (Box 112, Folder 1287-1290)
    Optical instruments, Chemical apparatus, etc.
  - Germicide Company of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1881; Uai +G317; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1291)
    "Germicide" apparatus for plumbing
  - Gibbons, Stanley, Limited (London England), 1936; Uai +G352; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1292)
    "Ideal" and "Imperial" stamp albums
  - Gibson Electric Company (New York, N.Y.), 1888; Uai +G359; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1294)
    Storage batteries
  - Gibson, Wm. D., Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1912; Uai G358; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1293)
  - Gielow, Henry J., Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1931; Uai +G362; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1295)
  - Gifford-Wood Company (Arlington, Mass.), 1905; Uai G366; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1296)
    Ice tools, elevators, and conveyors
  - Gilbert, A.C., Company (New Haven, Conn.), undated; Uai G376; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1297)
    "Kitchen Kit" electric mixer
  - Gilbert, Manufacturing Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1914; Uai G377; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1298)
    Automobile accessories
  - Gilette Safety Razor Company (Boston, Mass., etc.), undated; 2 volumes (Box 399, Folder 4308)
    Razors
  - Gillette Clipping Machine Company (New York, N.Y.), 1907; Uai G4136; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1299)
    Horse clipping and grooming machines
  - Gisholt Machine Company (Madison, Wis.), 1917; Uai +G446; 5 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1300-1301)
    Lathes, Tool grinders, etc.
  - Gisholt Machine Company (Madison, Wis.), undated; 2 volumes (Box 399, Folder 4309)
    Precision balancing machines
  - Gits Brothers Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1949; Uai +G448; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1302)
    Shaft seals lubricating devices
  - Glardon, Antoine (New York, N.Y.), 1913; Uai +G459; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1303)
    Glardon Swiss files
  - Glasgow Iron Company (Pottstown, Pa.), 1906–1920; Uai G462; 7 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1304-1309)
    Iron and steel plates, Muck bars, Flanged and press work, etc.
  - Glass Coffee Brewer Corporation (Chicago, Ill.), 1939; Uai G464; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1310)
    Cory coffee brewer
  - Glass Fibers Inc. (Toledo, Ohio), undated; Uai +G465; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1311)
    Glass fiber textile yarns
  - Gleason Works (Rochester, N.Y.), undated; Uai G477; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1313)
    Bevel gear machinery
  - Gleason-Tiebout Glass Company (New York, N.Y.), 1929; Uai +G476; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1312)
    Celestialite
  - Glen Brothers, Inc. (Rochester, N.Y.), 1929; Uai +G485; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1314)
    Bulbs, Plants, etc.
  - Glen Saint Mary Nurseries (Glen Saint Mary, Fla.), 1912; Uai G486; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1315)
    Fruit, Plants, etc.
  - Globe Company (Boston, Mass.), 1880–1899; Uai +G491; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1316)
    Berne smoke, spark, gas, and steam consumer, Business furniture, etc.
  - Globe Ticket Company of New England (Boston, Mass.), 1931; Uai G513; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1317)
    Tickets
  - Globe-Wernicke Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1900–1927; Uai +G515; 10 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1318-1320)
    Bookcases, Filing systems, etc.
  - Glyco Products Company (New York, N.Y), 1934; Uai G525; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1321)
  - Goddard and Goddard Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1949; Uai +G55; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1323)
    Carbide tipped cutters
  - Goerz, C. P., American Optical Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911–1919; Uai G553; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1325)
  - Goheen Manufacturing Company (Canton, Ohio, London, England), 1898–1909; Uai +G559; 4 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1326)
    Paints
  - Gold's Heater Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1879–1883; Uai +G57; 3 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1332)
    Heaters
  - Gold, Edward E., and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1877–1882; Uai +G562; 3 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1327)
    Railway car heaters, Wrought and cast-iron furnaces, etc.
  - Goldbach, C. (Kehl a. Rh., Germany), 1881–1882; Uai +G564; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1328)
  - Goldbacher, Ernest (New York, N.Y.), 1885; Uai +G565; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1329)
    Optical instruments, Thermometers, Compasses, etc.
  - Goldberg Display Fixtures (New York, N.Y.), 1915; Uai +G566; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1330)
    Folding display cases
  - Golden-Anderson Valve Specialty Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1914–1916; Uai +G567; 2 volumes (Box 113, Folder 1331)
  - Goldschmidt Thermit Company (New York, N.Y.), 1910; Uai +G572; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1333)
    Welding equipment
  - Goldsmith, L., and Son (Newark, N.J.), 1910; Uai G576; 1 volume (Box 113, Folder 1334)
    Trunks